- Welcome back to "Dance Stage USA."
Our next song is Sia's "Cheap Thrills."
Have you heard the song?
- Yes, I have.
- And what do you think?
- I think it's got a good
beat and you can dance to it.
- Sounds well, let's listen now.
♪ Up with it, girl ♪
♪ Rock with it, girl ♪
♪ Sia ♪
♪ Show them it, girl ♪
♪ Bada bang bang ♪
♪ Bounce with it, girl ♪
♪ Dance with it, girl ♪
♪ Get with it, girl ♪
♪ Bada bang bang ♪
♪ Come on, come on, turn the radio on ♪
♪ It's Friday night and it won't be long ♪
♪ Gotta do my hair, put my make-up on ♪
♪ 'Til I hit the dance floor ♪
♪ Bada bang ♪
♪ Hit the dance floor ♪
♪ I got all I need ♪
♪ No I ain't got cash, I ain't got cash ♪
♪ But I got you, baby ♪
♪ Just you and me ♪
♪ Baby, I don't need dollar
bills to have fun tonight ♪
♪ I love cheap thrills ♪
♪ Baby, I don't need dollar
bills to have fun tonight ♪
♪ I love cheap thrills ♪
♪ I don't need no money ♪
♪ You worth more than
diamond, more than gold ♪
♪ As long as I can feel the beat ♪
♪ Mek di beat just tek control ♪
♪ I don't need no money ♪
♪ You worth more than
diamond, more than gold ♪
♪ As long as I keep dancing ♪
♪ Free up yourself, get outta control ♪
♪ Come on, come on, turn the radio on ♪
♪ It's Saturday and it won't be long ♪
♪ Gotta paint my nails,
put my high heels on ♪
♪ It's Saturday and I won't be long ♪
♪ 'Til I hit the dance floor ♪
♪ Bada bang ♪
♪ Hit the dance floor ♪
♪ I got all I need ♪
♪ Sia ♪
♪ No, I ain't got cash, I ain't got cash ♪
♪ But I got you, baby ♪
♪ Just you and me ♪
♪ Baby, I don't need dollar
bills to have fun tonight ♪
♪ I love cheap thrills ♪
♪ Baby, I don't need dollar
bills to have fun tonight ♪
♪ I love cheap thrills ♪
♪ I don't need no money ♪
♪ You worth more than
diamond, more than gold ♪
♪ As long as I can feel the beat ♪
♪ Mek di beat just tek control ♪
♪ I don't need no money ♪
♪ You worth more than
diamond, more than gold ♪
♪ As long as I keep dancing ♪
♪ Free up yourself, get outta control ♪
♪ Me and you, girl, you and me ♪
♪ Drop it to di floor and mek
mi see your energy because ♪
♪ Mi nah play no hide and seek ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Wah fi see di ting you have ♪
♪ Weh mek mi feel weak, girl ♪
♪ Free ♪
♪ 'Cause anytime you wine an kotch it ♪
♪ Di selector pull it up and
put it pon repeat, girl ♪
♪ I'm nah touch a dollar in mi pocket ♪
♪ 'Cause nothin' in this world ♪
♪ Ain't more than what you worth ♪
♪ I don't need no money ♪
♪ You worth more than
diamond, more than gold ♪
♪ As long as I can feel the beat ♪
♪ Mek di beat just tek control ♪
♪ I don't need no money ♪
♪ You worth more than
diamond, more than gold ♪
♪ As long as I keep dancing ♪
♪ Free up yourself get outta control ♪
♪ Baby, I don't need dollar
bills to have fun tonight ♪
♪ I love cheap thrills ♪
♪ Baby, I don't need dollar
bills to have fun tonight ♪
♪ I love cheap thrills ♪
♪ I don't need no money ♪
♪ You worth more than
diamond, more than gold ♪
♪ As long as I can feel the beat ♪
♪ Mek di beat just tek control ♪
♪ I don't need no money ♪
♪ You worth more than
diamond, more than gold ♪
♪ As long as I keep dancing ♪
♪ Free up yourself get outta control ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ I love cheap trills ♪
(audio scratching)